https://www.achallenge.com/t-privacy.aspx

Search
Login    Cart: 0 item(s)
Now In: Privacy Policy
OUR PRIVACY STATEMENT
We thank you for visiting us on the Internet. We are committed to protecting your privacy while you browse and shop with use. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about When and Why we collect Personal Information.
WHEN and WHY
1. Ordering
When you place an order we collect Personal Information (such as name, contact and billing information, credit card, and other transaction information). We use this information to deliver your order, process payment, and to communicate with you about the status of your order.
2. Credit Card Storage
Credit card information collected for shopping cart orders is used only to process payment for the transaction and we do not retain the information on our website server. You may request that we store this information on a separate server that is not part of our web based computer system.
3. Surveys and Promotions
From time to time you may voluntarily provide Personal Information to complete surveys and questionnaires or to participate in user polls. We use this information to improve our products and services. We may also use your Personal Information to provide you newsletters and other marketing information. You may request to not receive emails from us, at which point your Personal Information will be removed from our electronic marketing system.
A LITTLE BIT MORE INFO. FOR YOU
Sharing Your Information
We do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personal Information we collect online. Personal Information you provide to us is stored in our databases in the United States.
Links To Other Web Sites
Links to third-party Web sites are provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide additional shopping for various other goods and services through non-affiliated partners. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. Please review the privacy policies of each site you visit.
Children's Privacy Protection
We take special care to protect the privacy needs of children and encourage parents to be an active participant in their child's online activities. Our Site does not target and is not intended for children. We market and sell to Clubs, Leagues, Teams and Adult consumers. We will not knowingly collect Personal Information from Children. If we discover personal data from a child through our Site, we will eliminate that data.
Contact Us
If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to to Customer Service (the button is on the bottom of the website, In the Black bar highlighted in Royal Blue) or call 800.638.9112.
Search        Camps         Request A Catalog        Frequently Asked Questions          Contact Us                 About Us                 Privacy Policy
Customer Service: 1-800-638-9112
Monday - Friday 9:00 to 4:30 Eastern
Contact Customer Service
American Challenge 60 Corbin Ave, Unit N, Bay Shore,
NY 11706
©Copyright 2004-2010,
American Challenge. All Rights Reserved.
